ROSE RENIE CANLAS

804-503-2465 <u>rrbgc0512@gmail.com</u> <u>rrcanlas.github.io/works/</u>

web designer | web content editor

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization management industry. Skilled in User Experience (UX), WordPress, User Interface Design, Web Design, and HTML. Alumni of the Grow with Google Developer Scholarship in 2018 and have from Udacity's Front-End Developer nanodegree.

EXPERIENCE

JOIN THE JOURNEY

Web Designer I Web Content Editor I Volunteer Oct 2013 - Present

A Christ centered Nonprofit organization providing medical, educational, aid relief and bringing poverty solutions through micro-lending to poor communities in Haiti, Cameroon, Peru and the Philippines.

- Designs and manage web content of the organization's website.
- Integrated social media components.

TESTIMONIES OF HOPE

Web Designer I Volunteer

Dec 2013 - Jul 2016

An inter-cultural and devotion Nonprofit organization building a safe online community for Christians.

- Designed theme and user experience.
- Integrated Paypal plugin.
- Integrated social media components.
- · Developed digital and graphic posters.

FORTUNE LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY

Programmer

Aug 2001 - Feb 2006

Fortune Life Insurance is a private company providing life insurance products in the Philippines

- Managed the phases of project planning, system design, user- interface design, coding, documentation, implementation user-training and support functions.
- Prepared and maintained documentation and operating manuals of developed systems.
- Develop, test, and implement computer programs on multiple computer/operating system platforms.
- Maintained company's website.

SKILLS I TOOLS

Web Development
Graphic Design
Programming
HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
React
JavaScipt/jQuery
Git/Github
Photoshop
Visual Basic

EDUCATION

UDACITY

Jan 10 2018 - Oct 23 2018
Front-End Web Developer - Grow with
Google Challenge Scholarship
Recipient

AMA COMPUTER COLLEGE

Sept 1996 - Apr 1999 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

AMA COMPUTER LEARNING CENTER

Jun 1994 - May 1996 Graduate Certificate - Systems Design and Programming